A Guide to the Town of Leesburg Municipal Government Center Hanno Weber and Associates Records, 1985-1997, n.d.
Thomas Balch Library
    - Contract Accounting-Certificates of Payment, 1989-June 1990
    - Contract Accounting-Certificates of Payment, July 1990-1991
    - Contract Accounting-Certificates of Payment, 1989-June 1990
    - Contract Accounting-Certificates of Payment-Furnishings, 1989-1992
    - Contract Accounting-Certificates of Payment-Millwork, 1990-1994
    - Contract Accounting-Certificates of Insurance, 1989-1990
    - Contract Accounting-Guarantee File, 1992
    - Contract Accounting-Transfers to Ownership, 1990-1991
    - Construction Administration-Progress Photographs, 1989-1991
    - Construction Administration-Other Construction Photographs, 1989-1991
    - Construction Administration-Construction Observation Reports, 1989-1990
    - Construction Administration-Construction Observation Reports, 1991
    - Construction Administration-Owner Observation Reports, 1990-1991
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #1, 7 June 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #2, 23 June 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #3, 29 June 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #4, 11 July 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #5, 31 July 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #6, 17 August 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #7, 21 August 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #8, 29 August 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #9, 8 September 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #10, 14 September 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #11, 22 September 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #12, 29 September 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #13, 9 October 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #14, 13 October 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #15, 20 October 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #16, 25 October 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #17, 3 November 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #18, 15 November 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #19, 22 November 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #20, 28 November 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #21, 5 December 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #22, 14 December 1989
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #23, 23 January 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #24, 23 February 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #25, 2 March 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc. #26, 22 August 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc.-Parking Garage #1, 10 August 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc.-Parking Garage #2, 2 October 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc.-Parking Garage #3, 27 December 1990
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc.-Parking Garage #4 (Vol. I), 14 May 1991
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc.-Parking Garage #4 (Vol. II), 14 May 1991
    - Construction Administration-Report of Construction Observations by CGC, Inc.-Parking Garage #5, 7 August 1991
    - Construction Administration-Minutes of Construction Meetings, 1989
    - Construction Administration-Minutes of Construction Meetings, 1990-1991
    - Construction Administration-Minutes of Furnishings Meetings, 1990-1991
    - Construction Administration-Minutes of Millwork Meetings, 1990-1991
    - Construction Administration-Structural and Civil Test Reports, 1989
    - Construction Administration-Structural and Civil Test Reports, 1990-1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List Correspondence, 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 1/1A-2 Mechanical, Electrical, Plumbing, November 1990-June 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 1-3 General Furnishings, November 1990-August 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 1-1A Interior Finish Review, November 1990-March 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 1 Custom Millwork Furnishings, November 1990
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No 2-3 Custom Millwork Furnishings, January-November 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 2 Building Exterior, April-July 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 1-2 Construction Engineering, April-July 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No.1 Structural Engineering, June 1991
    - Construction Administration-Punch List No. 3 Parking Structure, June 1991
    - Construction Administration-Accident Reports, 1990
    - Construction Administration-Certificate of Occupancy and Completion, 1990-1993
    - Publicity-Dedication of Municipal Government Center, 1991-1992
    - Publicity-Correspondence with Vendors re: Photographs, 1990-1991
    - Publicity-Correspondence with Architecture and Design Publications, 1990-1993
    - Publicity-Requests for Photographs and Information, 1997
  - Folded Drawings and Blueprints
    - Product Information
    - Working Design Sketch (WDSK)
    - Other Sketches
    - Civil Engineer Correspondence
    - General Contractor/Construction Manager Correspondence
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-2.2 Excavation
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-2.7 Irrigation
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-3.1 Concrete Admixtures
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-3.2 Architectural Precast Concrete
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-4.1 Unit Masonry
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-5.1 Steel
    - 5.2 Miscellaneous Metals
  - Folded Drawings and Blueprints
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-5.2 [sic] Steel Stairs
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-5.3 Metal Decking
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-5.4 Light Gauge Framing
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-6.3 Millwork
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-7.5 Protective Membrane Roofing Assembly
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-7.6 Metal Roofing and Siding
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-7.8 Metal Framed Skylights
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-7.82 Unit Skylight
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-8.6 Aluminum Clad Wood Windows
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-8.9 Aluminum Doors
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-9.25 Interior Gypsum Board Construction
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-9.5 Acoustical Ceiling
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-9.65 Resilient Flooring
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-10.15 Toilet Partitions
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-10.2 Aluminum Louvers
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-10.35 Flag Poles
  - Folded Drawings and Blueprints
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-10.4 Architectural Signage
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-10.8 Toilet and Bath Accessories
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-11.16 Dock Bumpers
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-12.68 Foot Grilles
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-14.3 Elevator Cab
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-15.4 Plumbing
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-15.5 Fire Protection
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-15.7-8-9 HVAC
    - Architectural Shop Drawings-16 HVAC
    - Interior Shop Drawings-12.2 Millwork
  - Photographs
    - Project Management and Programming-Project Programming, 1987
      - Leesburg Government Office Interiors
    - Contractor Records-Other Contractors, 1990
      - Juniper Bushes, 25 October 1990
    - Construction Administration-Progress Photographs #1-41, taken by Stewart Brothers Photographers, Inc., 29 June 1989-11 July 1990
      - No. 1 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 29 June 1989
      - No. 2 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 29 June 1989
      - No. 3 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northwest, 29 June 1989
      - No. 4 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking West, 29 June 1989
      - No. 5 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 29 June 1989
      - No. 6 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 29 June 1989
      - No. 7 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 27 July 1989
      - No. 8 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 27 July 1989
      - No. 9 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northwest, 27 July 1989
      - No. 10 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Southeast, 11 September 1989
      - No. 11 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 11 September 1989
      - No. 12 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northwest, 11 October 1989
      - No. 13 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 11 October 1989
      - No. 14 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 11 October 1989
      - No. 15 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northwest, 14 November 1989
      - No. 16 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 14 November 1989
      - No. 17 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Southeast, 14 November 1989
      - No. 18 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 13 December 1989
      - No. 19 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 13 December 1989
      - No. 20 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 13 December 1989
      - No. 21 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 16 January 1990
      - No. 22 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 16 January 1990
      - No. 23 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 16 January 1990
      - No. 24 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 13 February 1990
      - No. 25 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 13 February 1990
      - No. 26 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 13 February 1990
      - No. 27 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northwest, 14 March 1990
      - No. 28 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 14 March 1990
      - No. 29 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Southeast, 14 March 1990
      - No. 30 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 12 April 1990
      - No. 31 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 12 April 1990
      - No. 32 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 12 April 1990
      - No. 33 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 14 May 1990
      - No. 34 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 14 May 1990
      - No. 35 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 14 May 1990
      - No. 36 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking West, 13 June 1990
      - No. 37 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 13 June 1990
      - No. 38 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 13 June 1990
      - No. 39 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 11 July 1990
      - No. 40 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 11 July 1990
      - No. 41 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking West, 11 July 1990
    - Construction Administration- Progress Photographs #42-89, taken by Stewart Brothers Photographers, Inc., 9 August 1990-11 June 1991
      - No. 42 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 9 August 1990
      - No. 43 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 9 August 1990
      - No. 44 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking West, 9 August 1990
      - No. 45 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 11 September 1990
      - No. 46 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Southwest, 11 September 1990
      - No. 47 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking North, 11 September 1990
      - No. 48 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; View Looking Northeast at Parking Garage, 9 October 1990
      - No. 49 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; View Looking Northwest at Parking Garage, 9 October 1990
      - No. 50 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; View Looking Southwest at Parking Garage, 9 October 1990
      - No. 51 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 9 October 1990
      - No. 52 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Southwest, 9 October 1990
      - No. 53 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking Northeast, 9 October 1990
      - No. 54 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking South, 7 November 1990
      - No. 55 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking West, 7 November 1990
      - No. 56 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; General View Looking East, 7 November 1990
      - No. 57 Leesburg Municipal Government Center; Looking South at Parking Garage, 7 November 1990